How do you say "grilled cheese"?
-Hello.
-Hi.
I'm on my way from the airport,
and the front desk won't
get me your room number.
What's your room number?
-403.
-See you in half an hour.
-Wait a second.
-What?
-Where are you?
-I'm here.
I didn't say you could come here.
Can I come there?
OK.
I'll see you in half an hour.
What's this music?
How did you find me?
It wasn't actually that hard.
Are you going to take a bath?
It's for you.
What got you here?
Bar in the lobby.
What the fuck is going on?
How long have you been
at this hotel now?
I don't know.
More than a week?
More than a week.
More than a month?
More than a month.
How much does it cost?
I think around
750 million euros or something.
How long are you gonna stay?
How long do you wanna stay?
I'm leaving tomorrow morning.
I think it's time for you to go home.
Probably.
Are you running away from me?
I thought I already did.
Would you order me
a Bloody Mary, please?
Two Bloody Maries, please.
Have you slept with anyone?
No.
Have you?
That was a long pause.
-I guess it doesn't really matter.
-No, it doesn't.
You got bruises on your body.
Whatever happens in the end,
I don't wanna lose you as my friend.
I promise...
I will never be your friend...
no matter what.
Ever.
We fuck, then I'll feel
like shit tomorrow.
That's OK with me.
I love you.
I never hurt you on purpose.
I don't care.
Wanna see my view of Paris?
OK.